Great.
I'll bring it back for testing right away.
You brat.
Are you okay?
They give me maintenance doses regularly.
Don't worry, I won't die.
Thanks for your hard work.
By the way, Master.
How is the investigation going?
No progress.
There have been a few more victims
recently.
Some are beggars.
Some are dock workers.
And some are orphans.
These people either went missing
or died.
They all died in a miserable state.
I suspect they took drugs
before they died.
It should be a new type of drug.
Perhaps,
this is it.
We couldn't find a sample before.
Now we have one.
The Shisha Gang is closely related
to this.
Once I gain Xu Qingdao's trust,
I should be able to get more
inside information.
By the way.
What exactly happened
the day Lu Wenbiao died?
[Eclipse in the Lost City]
[Episode 8]
At that time, the bureau received news
that Lu Wenbiao was smuggling drugs
and preparing to abscond,
so I went after him.
But Lu Wenbiao was very calm.
I found it a bit strange
and wanted to interrogate him.
So I didn't want to shoot him at the time.
I even missed on purpose.
However,
from the same angle...
Someone fired a shot.
I checked that gun.
It was tampered with.
The bullets were also replaced.
Master, did you find out who it was?
Not yet.
But it proves our guess was right.
There is indeed a mole
in the police department.
Fortunately, he should've believed
the act we put on earlier,
that we have turned against each other.
When he lets his guard down,
he will definitely expose himself.
Also,
after the goods Lu Wenbiao transported
were confiscated by the police,
the warehouse inexplicably exploded.
Nothing was left.
Do you think he transported it
voluntarily?
Given Old Chief Lu's character,
he wouldn't do this.
I think so too.
Lu Wenbiao's drug trafficking incident
is not that simple.
You brat.
You even copy this.
Tell me about you.
How are you doing at Lu Ye's?
Seems not so well.
He hates me.
Hate.
It's good to be young.
You still have the energy to hate.
That kid has some tricks.
You be careful.
Got it, Master.
However,
being careful is useless.
He won't let me go.
By the way, Master.
What about that batch of arms?
Leave it to me.
You don't need to worry about it.
Young Master.
The arms at the train station,
as you ordered,
have been distributed to the branches.
Young Master.
You have truly become the man Master
expected you to be.
People change.
Just like the skies over Ningcheng.
They’re about to change too.
You've got some nerve,
cooking the books in front of me.
Damn it, that cop!
Stealing my thunder as soon as he arrives.
Just wait.
Let's go.
To Tianjiu Alley.
Hui.
Isn't that the Qingtian Gang's
most valued territory?
I haven't settled the score with Lu Ye
from last time.
I'm going to slap him hard in the face.
I want everyone to see
that Shen Tianbai isn't the only one
in the Shisha Gang who can fight.
What are you doing?
Step back.
Get lost.
Hui.
What do you mean by sealing this well?
The water from the well in Tianjiu Alley,
you've all drunk it, right?
Yes.
Is it sweet?
Do you know why it's so sweet?
Because under Tianjiu Alley
buries the ancestors of our Shisha Gang.
Drinking the water from this well
is like sucking the blood
of our Shisha Gang.
It's not too much to ask you
to pay some money, is it?
What?
We have to pay?
How could we afford it?
I'll let you off easy today.
I won't charge per person.
Half a silver dollar per household
every week.
How about that?
Half a silver dollar?
How could we possibly afford that?
Hui,
we all run small businesses.
Please have mercy on us.
That's none of my business.
If you can't pay, use the land
to settle the debt.
Hui,
this used to be the territory of Chief Lu
of the Qingtian Gang.
How do we use it to pay the debt?
Lu Wenbiao has been dead for a long time.
No one is protecting you anymore.
Either pay up or get lost.
I'm laying it on the line today.
Tomorrow,
if I don't see the money,
I'll make you suffer.
Hui...
Poor bastards.
Let's go.
Young Master.
The Shisha Gang went to the Tianjiu Alley
to collect protection fees.
They even charge for a sip of water.
The people living in there are all poor.
The old chief used to protect them.
As soon as he passed,
the Shisha Gang went to stir up trouble.
This is really going too far.
Who did it?
Hui.
He sure knows how to calculate.
First, he extorts money,
getting as much as he can.
Once everyone is driven away,
that territory will belong
to the Shisha Gang.
You really are capable.
You've only been in there for a few days,
and you've already caused so much trouble.
Do you mean this has something to do
with Shen Tianbai?
He's been showing off in the Shisha Gang,
becoming Xu Qingdao's right-hand man.
Others naturally feel a sense of crisis.
When people panic, they tend to do
stupid things.
Then, how should we handle this?
Give them money.
Give him the money.
I guessed it right.
Hui, you haven't changed a bit
over the decades.
As soon as you make some money,
you come to Dashijie to have fun.
Look who it is.
Isn't it Young Master Lu?
What?
Is the Qingtian Gang out of money,
so they sent you to shine shoes again?
Give me a shine.
If you do a good job,
I'll reward you with a drink.
Let me buy you a drink today, Hui.
You what?
You're awake.
The knockout drops of our Qingtian Gang
work pretty well, right?
You brat.
You dare to tie me up?
I'll make you pay for this.
Collecting money in Tianjiu Alley,
did you have fun?
So it's about this.
Why?
You still think that's
the Qingtian Gang's territory?
I collected the money.
I had a great time!
Glad you had fun.
After all, it's the price for your life.
Lu Ye, what are you doing?
I heard Hui slapped the Qingtian Gang
in the face at Tianjiu Alley.
That's so satisfying.
But why hasn't Hui come back yet?
There's something wrong with this wine.
Lu Ye.
What are you doing?
Don't you like water?
Then I'll let you drink your fill.
If I die,
the Shisha Gang won't let you off.
Then I'll be waiting.
Don't worry.
When that day comes,
I'll burn paper money to tell you.
You...
You're a madman.
You just found out?
Didn't Shen Tianbai tell you?
It's time to go.
Let him go.
You got here fast.
You really have a dog's nose.
Get out of the way.
Shen Tianbai.
Do you know why I want to kill him?
He broke into Tianjiu Alley,
collecting protection money
from every household,
half a silver dollar a week.
Who lives in Tianjiu Alley?
Shen Tianbai.
You should know better than me.